thinkproperty.com.my 2018-04-05

# Privacy Policy

**Company information**  
thinkproperty.my is owned by Think iProperty Sdn. Bhd. 

**Introduction**  
We are committed to protecting your privacy. This policy explains how and for what purposes we use the information collected about you on www.thinkproperty.my. Please read this privacy policy carefully. By using our website, you are agreeing to be bound by this policy.

 **Personal information collected**  
When you register on this website, you will be asked to provide certain information about yourself, including your name and your contact details. We may also collect information about how you use this website including your searches, the properties you look at, members you contact and the contents of the messages you send to them. Finally, we may also collect information from any correspondence that you have with us.

 **Use of personal information**  
Your information will enable us to provide the services and features that you have requested. We may use the information to identify patterns which we can use in our marketing and to help us administer and improve our services and features. We may use your information to notify you occasionally about important changes or developments to this website or our services, or about news which may be of interest to you. If you would prefer not to receive this information, please email us at [admin@thinkproperty.com.my](mailto:admin@thinkproperty.com.my). 

**Access to personal information**  
When our service is available via the websites of our partners, those partners may have access to your information. Their use of your personal information is governed by their privacy policies. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of any other websites, even if you access them using links from this website or if you can access this website or use our services from them.

 If our business enters into a joint venture with or is sold to or merged with another business entity, your information may be disclosed to our new business partners or owners.

If we offer a service to you from the website that is provided by a third party we may have to pass your information to them in order to deliver the service. By using such services you consent to us providing your information to the third party. We may also use third parties to provide services on our behalf which may include processing (but not using themselves) your information. 

We will not otherwise disclose, sell or distribute your information to any third party without your permission unless we are required to do so by law.

 **Cookies**  
Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enable us to personalise your visits to this website, simplify the signing-in procedure, keep track of your preferences and to track the usage of this website. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored in the hard drive of your computer by your browser. Your browser will have the option to prevent websites using cookies (your browser's help screen or manual will tell you how to do this), but please note that this may reduce the functionality of this website and other websites.

Like most websites, our servers automatically record 'log files' containing information about the volume and characteristics of our website traffic e.g. IP address, numbers of pages viewed, length of time spent on site. We use log files to build pictures of how our site is used that help us to monitor and improve the service. We cannot identify you from your log files.

 **Changes to the policy**  
We may change this policy from time to time as we add new services or features or in response to changes in the law or our commercial arrangements. Any changes to this policy will be posted on this website.
